It's always been about me, myself and I
曾经  我是个单身主义者
I thought relationships were nothing but a waste of time
爱情只会浪费我的时间
I never wanted to be anybody's other half
我从没想过要成为别人的另一半
I was happy saying I had a love that wouldn't last
爱上我 不会有结果
That was the only way I knew till I met you
这就是我  直到我遇见了你
You make we wanna say. I do, I do, I do, do do do do do do do
我想告诉你 我真的  我真的愿意
Yeah, I do, I do, I do, do do do do do do do
我真得  我真的愿意  因为你
Cause every time before it's been like. Maybe yes and maybe no
这要是在以前 我就爱理不理
I can't live without it, I can't let it go
可现在我放不下你  我真的放不下
Ooh, what did I get myself into?
唉 我到底是着魔了还是怎么
You make we wanna say I do, I do, I do, I do, I do, I do  I do. Love you
我想告诉你  我真的真的 只爱你